Kamran Waris

Lahore, Punjab, Pakistan

mailsicoding@gmail.com

+923020707150

linkedin.com/in/mailsi-coding

Summary

Hi, I am Kamran Waris professional developer with more than 1 year of experience in PHP Laravel Development. My professional skills include Laravel, Core PHP, JavaScript, jQuery, Restful Web APIs, HTML5, CSS3 and Bootstrap. I will use all my skills and experience to deliver the best product for you. I have worked on multiple projects and on many e-commerce websites and I will surely be a help to your business growth. Client satisfaction is my success.

Experience



PHP Laravel Developer

LEADconcept

Feb 2022 - Present (3 months +)

Highapp Solution Mar 2021 - Feb 2022 (1 year)

Student

Self-employed

Oct 2018 - Feb 2022 (3 years 5 months)



Wordpress Developer

Housecodies (Pvt) Ltd Jun 2020 - Mar 2021 (10 months)

Education



University of Engineering and Technology, Lahore

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science 2018 - 2022

Skills

PHP Laravel • WordPress • Web Design • Web Development • LARAVEL • Bootstrap • PHP